





Master student in computer science with software engineer co-op experience at Wasabi Technologies. Forward-thinking and adaptable engineer in software development field with passion on clean code and efficient algorithm implementation. Blends drive for excellence with humor and generosity.

### **EDUCATION**

## M.Sc in Computer Science — Northeastern University (GPA 3.9/4.0)

May 2020, Boston, MA

Main Courses: Data Structures, Object-Oriented Design, Algorithm, Computer System, Parallel Processing in MapReduce Web Development, Database Management, Reinforcement Learning

**Skill Sets**: Java, Golang, Python, Javascript, ReactJS, Node.js, HTML, CSS, MySQL, MongoDB, MapReduce, AWS (S3, EMR), Docker, RabbitMQ, Git.

B.Sc in Electronic Information Science and Technology — Nankai University (GPA 3.3/4.0)

June 2012, Tianjin, China

Main Courses: Theory of Telecommunication, Signal and System Activity: Nankai University Community Volunteer Program

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Software Engineer Intern — Wasabi Technologies

January 2019 – August 2019

- Developed a notification service system and integrated it with current cloud storage product to provide storage event notification for user through Http protocol. Built the notification service using Golang through Publish-Subscriber model in the backend. Utilized Golang multiple threading and RabbitMQ for handling an estimated 4K/s per storage object notification event message flow in the system. Created the front-end notification configuration UI into the current storage console application through React. Used docker to containerize the notification system as an independent deployable application. The service launched in the company's Q3 release cycle.
- Built a full-stack authentication system with enterprise single-sign-on function into the current cloud storage product. Implemented the backend login, authentication and REST service using Golang and front-end UI app using React. Integrated the system with external cloud identity provider Okta, Auth0 and Shibboleth using OpenID and SAML authentication protocol. The system went live in company's Q2 release cycle and opened for major customer use.
- Created technical development documentations for both authentication system and notification system. Assisted customer support team to generate product knowledge document of this two new services for customers.

#### Radio Network Engineer — Ericsson.Inc

August 2012 – May 2017

- Performed technical support for 7 Ericsson's LTE network projects globally including Asia, Australia and North American market.
- Led customer relation management and project management for Ericsson LTE network roll out projects of DTAC mobile.
- Acted as team leader of 20 LTE engineers and lead to deploy over 3000 LTE base stations in the urban Bangkok area.
- Built up team LTE competence as technical mentor through Ericsson mentorship program for new LTE engineers.

## **ACADEMIC PROJECTS**

## Course Management Platform - MERN Stack Web Application

September 2018 – October 2018

- Built a web course management system using React which could let faculty create, modify courses and student browser courses.
- Designed UI components with React Material UI suite for managing faculty account information and modifying, previewing course modules, lessons, topics and widgets. Managed components states using Redux.
- Generated RESTful data service as middle tier using Java Spring Boot for managing faculty and course data. Deployed MySQL database to store faculty and course data in server side through JPA.
- Created ChatBot using Google DialogFlow AI API to response users's question about the course management platform automatically.

#### Tweet User Connection Graph Analysis - MapReduce Application

September 2018 – October 2018

- Built a MapReduce Java program to calculate the longest shortest path of random select k users to every user in the tweet user graph.
- Deployed the MapReduce program on AWS S3 and EMR service using 10 EC2 machines to analyze 1.32G tweet user connection data and got the user's average longest connection diameter of 7 users.

# Stock Application – MVC Java Application

March 2018 - April 2018

- Built a Java stock application to let user create, manage personal stock portfolio and view real-time stock price trend.
- Constructed stock market model through which user can manage personal stock portfolio like buying, selling shares.
- Created stock data model interface to retrieving over 200 real-time stock data by exploiting Alpha Vintage Stock API.
- Designed Java Swing interactive graphical view to display user stock portfolio price trend and implemented a Simple Moving Average KPI algorithm to highlight buying opportunity.